<resources>

    <string name="title_home">Home</string>
    <string name="title_dashboard">Dashboard</string>
    <string name="title_notifications">Notifications</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string-array name="music_list">
        <item>Say My Name</item>
        <item>Ending of Beginning</item>
        <item>Paranoia</item>
    </string-array>
        <string name="app_name">PEPO</string>
        <string name="home">Home</string>
        <string name="letra">Letra</string>
        <string name="config">Configurações</string>
        <string name="sair">Sair</string>
        <string name="tema">Tema</string>
        <string name="waitingMusic">carregando musica</string>
    <string name="paranoia">
        Two sides to a story but they never tell my side
        Never been the kinda guy to stay inside the guidelines
        I know Im the bad guy, I dont gotta ask why
        If you try step to me, itll be the last time
        I got dirt on my name, six feet in the ground
        I got people in my past try bringin me down
        Say Im losin my mind, I dont wanna be found
        Grew up in the shadow but I know they watchin me now
        Paranoia, on the go, Im moving silent (lets go)
        Pull up on ya, I got trouble right behind me (lets go)
        Bite the bullet, suit and tie, the silver linin
        Im-im-im-im gonna show you how to crash a party
        Every time you pop off, they hopin that you fall hard
        They prayin for the death of a rockstar
        Everybody hatin ever since you got more
        They prayin for the death of a rockstar
        Ooh, they love it when you lost, boy
        Now the low life at the top floor
        Everybody hatin ever since you got more
        They prayin for the death of a rockstar
        They talk about me, I forget to listen
        At least I get the recognition
        Heavyweight, I pull up on you with the repetition
        You in the pit, its not no exhibition
        Oh, they big mad, Im the big boss
        Talk a big game, take a big loss
        Growin up, I was the problem that they didnt solve
        Im the piece that wouldnt fit inside the jigsaw
        I got a lotta punch lines and a quick jab
        Im runnin straight through, I dont gotta zig-zag
        I got a heavy heart, its hard to lift that
        From the cradle to the grave, never changed, make em dig that
        Paranoia, on the go, Im moving silent (lets go)
        Pull up on ya, I got trouble right behind me (lets go)
        Bite the bullet, suit and tie, the silver linin
        Im-im-im-im gonna show you how to crash a party
        Every time you pop off, they hopin that you fall hard
        They prayin for the death of a rockstar
        Everybody hatin ever since you got more
        They prayin for the death of a rockstar
        Ooh, they love it when you lost, boy
        Now the low life at the top floor
        Everybody hatin ever since you got more
        They prayin for the death of a rockstar
        They wanna kiss me long good night with a rose
        Hoping that the Eiffel falls, of course
        You dont understand the life we chose
        (On life support, life goes)
        I need my silence, my privacy so I can heal
        And even rockstars got feelings that they feel
        In reality, this just repeats like a drill
        Always, oh-oh, oh-oh
        Every time you pop off, they hopin that you fall hard
        They prayin for the death of a rockstar (yeah, yeah)
        Everybody hatin ever since you got more
        They prayin for the death of a rockstar
        Ooh, they love it when you lost, boy (when you lost)
        Now the low life at the top floor (top floor)
        Everybody hatin ever since you got more (ever since you got more)
        They prayin for the death of a rockstar
        Pop off, they hopin that you fall hard
        They prayin for the death of a rockstar
        Everybody hatin ever since you got more (ever since you got more)
        They prayin for the death of a rockstar
    </string>
    <string name="saymyname">
        You could use a buddy
        Dont you want a pal?
        (Yes I do! Yes I do)
        Girl, the way I see it
        Your daddy should be leavin
        And you should stick around
        What?
        Nothing
        So, Lydia, dont end yourself
        Defend yourself
        Daddy is the one you should maim
        Together well exterminate, assassinate
        No
        The finer points can wait
        But first you gotta say my name
        Go ahead and jump but that wont stop him
        Here you got a solid plan B option
        I can bring your daddy so much pain
        All you gotta do is say my name
        Girl, just say it three times in a row
        And you wont believe how far Ill go
        Im on the bench, but coach
        Just put me in the game
        All you gotta do is say my name
        I dont know your name
        Well, I cant say it
        How bout a game of charades?
        Yes, lets play it
        Two words
        Right
        Second word
        Uh-huh
        Drink?
        No
        Beverage?
        No
        Wine?
        No
        Juice?
        Yes
        Okay
        First word
        Okay
        Bug?
        No
        Ant?
        Close, but no
        Beetle?
        Yes
        Beetlejuice ?
        Wow, Im impressed
        And all you gotta do is say my name three times
        Three times in a row it must be spoken unbroken
        Ready?
        Yeah
        Okay, go
        Beetlejuice
        Yes
        Beetlejuice
        Yes
        Be
        Oh, oh, this is gonna be so good
        Cause
        What?
        Youre so smart
        A stand-up bro
        Ill think about your offer
        Let you know
        But I prefer my chances down below
        Beetlejuice
        Yes
        Beetlejuice
        Yes
        Being young and female doesnt mean that Im an easy mark
        Ive been swimming with piranhas
        I dont need a shark
        Yes, life sucks
        But not that much
        Okay, Beetlejuice
        Beetlejuice
        Be a doll and spare the lecture
        Im offering you a full time specter
        But are you any good?
        You betcha
        Trust me, baby
        I just met ya
        Really its a flattering offer
        Dont you wanna see dad suffer?
        I think Id rather just jump off
        No
        I may be suicidal
        But Beetlejuice , its not as if Ive lost my mind
        So, playing hardball, huh?
        You are tougher than you look
        Just wanna make sure I know who Im working with
        Got any references?
        Lydia, there you are
        Are you alright?
        A-Dog, B-Town, my old pals
        You, get away from her
        Lydia, this is a dangerously unstable individual
        Beetlejuice is sexy
        Beetlejuice is smart
        BJ is a graduate of Juilliard
        He can help
        We found him on Yelp
        Our troubles all ended on the day that we befriended him
        Every word is the truth
        Beetlejuice , Beetlejuice , Beetlejuice
        What the heck was that?
        So violating
        There you go, kid
        Couple of five-star reviews
        What was that?
        That was possession
        Any ghost can do that in less than one lesson
        Any ghost?
        Pretty much, any ghostll do sure
        Then, Beetlejuice , what do I need you for?
        Woah, woah, woah woah woah
        Hold up, hold up, girl, Im your pal
        Theyre sweet, but Im a demon straight from Hell
        I know, I went a little hard on my sell
        But were BF-F-F-Fs forever
        Agh
        Lydia
        What? He was already dead
        And you heard what he said, any ghost can do that possession stuff
        We dont need that demon
        The three of us alone can wreck dads evening
        Together we can make a grown man weep
        Guys, I got a dinner date to keep
        Okay, so whats the plan?
        Teach dad a lesson
        Hes gonna freak when we possess him
        So he wants the perfect daughter
        Ill lead that lamb to slaughter
        Yeah, I got game
        Im gonna make him say my name
        (Make him say your name)
        Ill make him say my name
        (Make him say your name)
        Ill make him say my name
        (Make him say your name)
        Not running away
        Ill make him say my name
    </string>

    <string-array name="temas">
        <item>Melancia</item>
        <item>Maçã</item>
    </string-array>


</resources>